{
    "subject": "resource/Dinah_Shore",
    "predicate": "property/associatedActs",
    "object": "resource/Frank_Sinatra",
    "human_readable": "Dinah Shore was associated with Frank Sinatra.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9653959274291992,
            "question": "What was the nature of Dinah Shore's association with Frank Sinatra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9577414989471436,
            "question": "During what period were Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra associated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105944037437439,
            "question": "Who was Dinah Shore associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8805344700813293,
            "question": "Were Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7658275961875916,
            "question": "What other notable figures were part of the same entertainment circle as Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7215636372566223,
            "question": "Did Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra collaborate on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6223346590995789,
            "question": "What are some common themes in the music of Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3503964841365814,
            "question": "What is Frank Sinatra known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23269867897033691,
            "question": "In what genre of music was Dinah Shore popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20897109806537628,
            "question": "How did Dinah Shore's career impact the music industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dinah Shore was associated with Frank Sinatra.",
            "html": "dbpedia_995_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what genre of music was Dinah Shore popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_995_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Frank Sinatra known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_995_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in the music of Dinah Shore and Frank Sinatra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_995_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_995_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple statements about Dinah Shore and her association with Frank Sinatra. For example, it says \"Dinah Shore had a close friendship with Frank Sinatra\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_995/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt) and \"Frank Sinatra said he'd known Shore as a close friend for a half century\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_995/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt). These statements support the triple that Dinah Shore was associated with Frank Sinatra."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Dinah Shore was associated with Frank Sinatra, mentioning their close friendship and musical collaborations."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}